Hello Friends Anand Shukla today in this video we are going to tell you about the
diseases in health insurance like what are the symptoms, they are
never covered in any health insurance
policy, you should take a family floater policy for
pimples, you should take a policy from your family
floater policy, you should take a
policy from an advisor or you should take a
policy from an online portal,
today I am going to tell you about the fixed
acid which is 15GB health insurance
policy or your theme show
loot is not covered, let's talk about it, first of all if
you do something against the law, i.e. if the
policy holder accepts it, then it is not covered, for
example, if you drink and drive
and have an accident and have to get help for it,
and it is
written that you had consumed alcohol, then such
insurance is not covered, apart from this,
you can do some parateacher activities like
landing, mountain rafting, motor
racing and dealing with sports,
handwriting styles in these also, adventure
sports, health inspectors are never covered for
this  Apart from this, if someone is
consuming some anti-aging drug then that too is not the time to sleep,
he is walking down the street, that is, some
congenital problem, one of which is curd,
these things are also not covered, that
meeting salary or this water, it is
not covered, like any beauty mantra, if you are starting to
look old, you are getting anti-aging done
or getting a hair transplant,
this cosmetic is not covered today,
apart from this any transmission
related thing i.e. positive and
waste is not covered on the website, change which is fast
circuit minute gender change, back is
not covered, apart from this contract treatment, that is, it is often
heard that
a father has got a bed booked, for
which some plants are found in medical science, then
that too is 30 inch
back, it is not covered, after this we talk about
natural cure and K 235, these are also not covered,
any life style related thing
like regular consumption of this medicine
will measure the fit and the doctor has
seen this, or if the reason for liver damage is
excessive alcohol consumption, whether in his
proposal  If it is mentioned in the form, it is
not a death penalty, there is such insurance,
apart from this, mental illness i.e. depression or should
click is world famous psychiatric illness, its
obscene period will be subscribed and
infertility, if a woman does
not conceive a child and gets treated for it, then
that person is not covered like this,
apart from this, some medicines are taken for obesity, to
reduce obesity,
they also do not have natural benefits,
hence they are not covered, last but not the least important is
investigation of urination,
if there is any style vs new, the passenger
himself is feeling that Modi is right
that I have gone and got
admission for all the times today, then it is a
case of OPD, that health insurance is
not covered, you have
mentioned the names of many diseases in my insult, but
it is true that it is a
jhali, you are also more useful that
computers, there are many such things which
reduce after a month, like tabs, if
hard work has been done, that delivery ant,
when is a meeting in Badal Pistorius,
if the college flower will not be intact and
Even after 2 years, there are some such things that happen here and there.
If you have not seen that video of mine yet, then
I have posted its link,
you must watch that video. I will tell you that
after 2 years, diseases are covered.
You must have liked this video
of your health insurance which is positive. In this, you will
send some addition or wine
set or you can
like, share and subscribe to my YouTube channel.
Thank you.